[
    { "answer": "a", "question": "ア" },
    { "answer": "i", "question": "イ" },
    { "answer": "u", "question": "ウ" },
    { "answer": "e", "question": "エ" },
    { "answer": "o", "question": "オ" },
    { "answer": "ka", "question": "カ" },
    { "answer": "ki", "question": "キ" },
    { "answer": "ku", "question": "ク" },
    { "answer": "ke", "question": "ケ" },
    { "answer": "ko", "question": "コ" },
    { "answer": "sa", "question": "サ" },
    { "answer": "shi", "question": "シ" },
    { "answer": "su", "question": "ス" },
    { "answer": "se", "question": "セ" },
    { "answer": "so", "question": "ソ" },
    { "answer": "ta", "question": "タ" },
    { "answer": "chi", "question": "チ" },
    { "answer": "tsu", "question": "ツ" },
    { "answer": "te", "question": "テ" },
    { "answer": "to", "question": "ト" },
    { "answer": "na", "question": "ナ" },
    { "answer": "ni", "question": "ニ" },
    { "answer": "nu", "question": "ヌ" },
    { "answer": "ne", "question": "ネ" },
    { "answer": "no", "question": "ノ" },
    { "answer": "ha", "question": "ハ" },
    { "answer": "hi", "question": "ヒ" },
    { "answer": "fu", "question": "フ" },
    { "answer": "he", "question": "ヘ" },
    { "answer": "ho", "question": "ホ" },
    { "answer": "ma", "question": "マ" },
    { "answer": "mi", "question": "ミ" },
    { "answer": "mu", "question": "ム" },
    { "answer": "me", "question": "メ" },
    { "answer": "mo", "question": "モ" },
    { "answer": "ya", "question": "ヤ" },
    { "answer": "yu", "question": "ユ" },
    { "answer": "yo", "question": "ヨ" },
    { "answer": "ra", "question": "ラ" },
    { "answer": "ri", "question": "リ" },
    { "answer": "ru", "question": "ル" },
    { "answer": "re", "question": "レ" },
    { "answer": "ro", "question": "ロ" },
    { "answer": "wa", "question": "ワ" },
    { "answer": "wo", "question": "ヲ" },
    { "answer": "n", "question": "ン" }
]